 const quiz =  [
      {
        "question": "1.     How many different positions can you set for drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1",
        "option2" : "b)   2",
        "option3" : "c)   4",
        "option4" : "d)   6",
        "answer"  : "b)   2"
      },
      {
        "question": "2.     How many ways you can save a document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   4",
        "option3" : "c)   5",
        "option4" : "d)   6",
        "answer"  : "a)   3"
      },
      {
        "question": "3.     Single spacing in MS Word document causes - point line spacing ?",
        "option1" : "a)   10",
        "option2" : "b)   12",
        "option3" : "c)   14",
        "option4" : "d)   16",
        "answer"  : "b)   12"
      },
      {
        "question": "4.     What is the default number of lines to drop for drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   10",
        "option3" : "c)   15",
        "option4" : "d)   20",
        "answer"  : "a)   3"
      },
      {
        "question": "5.     What is the maximum number of lines you can set for a drop cap ?",
        "option1" : "a)   3",
        "option2" : "b)   10",
        "option3" : "c)   15",
        "option4" : "d)   20",
        "answer"  : "b)   10"
      },
      {
        "question": "6.     How many column can you insert in a word document in maximum ?",
        "option1" : "a)   35",
        "option2" : "b)   45",
        "option3" : "c)   55",
        "option4" : "d)   65",
        "answer"  : "b)   45"
      },
      {
        "question": "7.     In a document, What is the maximum number of columns that can be inserted in MS-Word Table ?",
        "option1" : "a)   35",
        "option2" : "b)   15",
        "option3" : "c)   63",
        "option4" : "d)   65",
        "answer"  : "c)   63"
      },
      {
        "question": "8.     What is the maximum scale percentage available in scale drop down box ?",
        "option1" : "a)   500",
        "option2" : "b)   200",
        "option3" : "c)   100",
        "option4" : "d)   90",
        "answer"  : "b)   200"
      },
      {
        "question": "9.     What is the maximum font size you can apply for any character ?",
        "option1" : "a)   163",
        "option2" : "b)   1638",
        "option3" : "c)   16038",
        "option4" : "d)   None of these",
        "answer"  : "b)   1638"
      },
      {
        "question": "10.     Word by default, places a tab step at every_mark on the ruler ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   2.5"',
        "option2" : 'b)   .5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   .75"',
        "option4" : 'd)   .1"',
        "answer"  : 'b)   .5"'
      },
      {
        "question": "11.     What is the default file extension for all word documents ?",
        "option1" : "a)   txt",
        "option2" : "b)   word",
        "option3" : "c)   docs",
        "option4" : "d)   docx",
        "answer"  : "d)   docx"
      },
      {
        "question": "12.     The file type_indicates the file is a word document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   .msw",
        "option2" : "b)   .wor",
        "option3" : "c)   .wrd",
        "option4" : "d)   .doc",
        "answer"  : "d)   .doc"
      },
      {
        "question": "13.     How much space in minimum must be provided between columns ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   0"',
        "option2" : 'b)   0.5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1"',
        "option4" : 'd)   1.5"',
        "answer"  : 'a)   0"'
      },
      {
        "question": "14.     What is the smallest width of column ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   0"',
        "option2" : 'b)   0.5"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1"',
        "option4" : 'd)   1.5"',
        "answer"  : 'd)   1.5"'
      },
      {
        "question": "15.     By default, your document print with ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 inch top and bottom margins",
        "option2" : "b)   A portrait orientation",
        "option3" : "c)   1.25 inches left and right margins",
        "option4" : "d)   All of the above",
        "answer"  : "b)   A portrait orientation"
      },
      {
        "question": "16.     Word is present to use standard 8.5 by 11 inch paper with_margins ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 inch left, right, top and bottom",
        "option2" : "b)   1.25 inch left, right top and bottom",
        "option3" : "c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button",
        "option4" : "d)   1 inch left and right margins and 1.25 inch top and bottom",
        "answer"  : "c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button"
      },
      {
        "question": "17.     What is the default left margin in word 2003 document ?",
        "option1" : 'a)   1"',
        "option2" : 'b)   1.25"',
        "option3" : 'c)   1.5"',
        "option4" : 'd)   2"',
        "answer"  : 'b)   1.25"(31.7mm)'
      },
      {
        "question": "18.     What is the smallest and largest font size available in font size tool on formatting toolbar ?",
        "option1" : "a)   8 and 72",
        "option2" : "b)   8 and 64",
        "option3" : "c)   12 and 72",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   8 and 72"
      },
      {
        "question": "19.     What is the default font size of a new word document based on normal template in word 2003 ?",
        "option1" : "a)   10pt",
        "option2" : "b)   12pt",
        "option3" : "c)   14pt",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "b)   12pt"
      },
      {
        "question": "20.     The minimum number of rows and columns in MS-Word document is ?",
        "option1" : "a)   1 and 1",
        "option2" : "b)   2 and 1",
        "option3" : "c)   2 and 2",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   1 and 1"
      },
      {
        "question": "21.     In mail merge operation which of the following might represent the main document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A scale brochure",
        "option2" : "b)   A form letter",
        "option3" : "c)   A database of Names and Addresses",
        "option4" : "d)   None of above",
        "answer"  : "a)   A scale brochure"
      },
      {
        "question": "22.     Pressing F8 key for three times select ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A word",
        "option2" : "b)   A sentense",
        "option3" : "c)   A paragraph",
        "option4" : "d)   entire document",
        "answer"  : "b)   A sentense"
      },
      {
        "question": "22.     What do you call a collection of character and paragraph formatting commands ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A style",
        "option2" : "b)   A template",
        "option3" : "c)   A style",
        "option4" : "d)   A boilerplate",
        "answer"  : "a)   A style"
      },
      {
        "question": "23.     What is document outline view ?",
        "option1" : "a)   A preview in a full screen",
        "option2" : "b)   A preview with margins",
        "option3" : "c)   A view with a margins and gutter",
        "option4" : "d)   A view with a structure of heading at various levels",
        "answer"  : "d)   A view with a structure of heading of various levels"
      },
      {
        "question": "24.     Ctrl+Z ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Undo the last action",
        "option2" : "b)   Redo the last action",
        "option3" : "c)   Add the new page",
        "option4" : "d)   Paste the contents clipboard",
        "answer"  : "a)   Undo the last action"
      },
      {
        "question": "25.     The ____ in the resume wizard dialog box indicates the wizard is ready to create the document ?",
        "option1" : "a)   Start panel",
        "option2" : "b)   Address panel",
        "option3" : "c)   Add/Sort Heading panel",
        "option4" : "d)   Finish panel",
        "answer"  : "d)   Finish panel"
      },

    ];
  

  export default quiz;